mytubecams.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy Policy | MyTubeCams

* * *

mytubecams.com will process any personal data according to legislation in respect of the processing of personal data, such as the European e-Privacy Directive (2009/136/EC).    

By using the services of mytubecams.com you give permission to mytubecams.com to process technical data related to your visit to the mytubecams.com website and personal data, including sensitive data (eg. relating to sexual life), provided by you or collected during the registration process, during the period of his subscription with mytubecams.com and after cancellation of your subscription during the period necessary for mytubecams.com to comply with legal requirements.

mytubecams.com does:

  * use your e-mail address only to create your account and provide you by e-mail with relevant information about the website mytubecams.com and (other) services of mytubecams.com;
  * only collect information for the purpose of running mytubecams.com and improving the services;
  * register the number of visits and areas of mytubecams.com-pages visited by you;
  * store private communications, such as telephone conversations, chat logs, faxes and letters to staff of mytubecams.com along with e-mail messages and chat logs which are sent by you through the mytubecams.com website (for a limited period of time, 12 months);
  * Use cookies (see below).

mytubecams.com does not share your information with third parties, except when required by law, or with explicit permission from you.

By using the website mytubecams.com you agree and allow mytubecams.com to collect, process and communicate to its processors, including the processors situated in countries not ensuring an adequate level of protection according to European Commission. 

mytubecams.com takes serious security measures to make sure any data is protected against unauthorized access.

You may ask for a copy of any personal information that mytubecams.com processes. You also has the right to ask for rectification of any incorrect personal data. I you want to obtain a copy of any personal information that mytubecams.com process and ask for rectification of any incorrect personal data, you can send an e-mail to: [support@globeconnect.net](mailto:support@globeconnect.net). If you would like to oppose the processing of personal data by mytubecams.com, you are entitled to cancel your use of the website mytubecams.com at any time.

Upon reception of the above mentioned request, mytubecams.com will communicate the personal data thats concerns you to the email address you provided during the registration process.

mytubecams.com makes use of cookies and logging in the website mytubecams.com and in its websites in order to make them more efficient.

A cookie is a small chunk of information that is saved by an application on your computer or device. Cookies are used to simplify and analyze the use of the website mytubecams.com. For instance, functional cookies are used to register your log in status, to prevent having to enter the same information with every (page)visit to the website mytubecams.com.

Some applications in the website mytubecams.com are only available with the use of cookies. Should you not wish to allow the use of cookies on your computer you have the option to configure your browser in such a way that it will notify you every time cookies are created or that the creation of them is blocked. This may result in certain aspects of the website mytubecams.com to not function properly, not being (properly) visible or in you being asked to enter your log in details more often.

Globe Connect Worldwide Ltd, located at: Westlandseweg 11, unit 1.25, 2291 PG Wateringen, The Netherlands (Registered by the Dutch Chamber of Commerce under registration number: 58753125.  

* * *
